You
Hold on I decide if we help
Okay, so what do we got interesting case
To say the least the suspect is cunning talking extremely meticulous this surveillance photo is all we have of him
What's the crime multiple homicides no obvious motive linking them we think we have a serial killer on our hands
It's a tough call without knowing how the victims are connected though
Clues are few and far between but we need this man off the streets right now
What kind of lunatic goes around killing random people were you talking about we have to help don't worry officer
No one else is going to die so fast loser. You don't stop for us. Remember?
Hi captain shall don't listen to this guy. How about it Lou? I've looked at the photos. No luck. I'm sorry
We can't help
Yeah, what for real just try again. Maybe you miss something. Come on. Let's go dummy
What gives you starting to get lazy shut up be glad that case on the leg it would have been intense
Trust his judgment
It didn't take too long to realize something has changed in the back of my mind your eyes
There ain't no way left to hide behind time no longer flew like it was when the flash froze everything before
Without you. I don't know if I could take this road
I'm about to lose my mind every minute that I die back in time every single existence rewinds
Some physical pain in this I drive
All the hardest and the smiles never faded. I know you'll be by my side when we make it
Come back from
Take back in time
Die back in time
And you're positive you saw everything clearly,
because I know you're not the kind to say no to a mission.
You're the one who wanted to take a break.
Oh, well, yeah.
But that was then, so I think I'm good now.
Look who I brought.
Hey, favorite landlady.
A guest has arrived.
Shouldn't you be off studying to be a doctor or something?
I dropped by because I heard you needed more work, something about debt.
I see. Slumming it with the idiots, huh? You're too kind.
So then, Miss Scholar, books driving you crazy yet?
Uh, I had to stay in school.
Unlike someone I know, I don't want to rely on others for handouts.
Hey, now! You got it wrong! I play a vital role here!
Ling put a roof over your head and Lu Guang manages the business
while you coast along making jokes!
We are partners!
Didn't anyone ever teach you not to talk crap if you don't have all the facts?
That makes you look like an idiot, smarty pay!
Quiet!
What if I told you, be nice and listen to our customers?
It's not hard.
But she's just a friend!
Wait, customer?
She convinced me to come and give you a chance.
It wasn't my idea.
So tell us, what can we help you with?
See?
I'll tell you the sad story.
Now picture it.
Our college years, days of youth and vigor!
Well, it hasn't been that long.
But there was another member of a friend group who was particularly fond of our dear Xu, Dong Yi.
I need to study.
Then, hold onto these for me.
I'll swing by your dorm and get them tonight.
Hey!
Make sure you're not too late or I'll have to throw him down from my window!
You two are like an old married couple.
Why not just tell him you want to be official?
Yeah.
That'd be nice.
But I want him to ask me.
Saved you a seat!
Morning.
Grabbed you a sandwich.
Eggs, sausage, and hot sauce.
Awesome!
Here.
I'll send you some cash.
Put your phone down.
This is a gift.
Can't I surprise my friend?
Uh…
Victory!
Alright!
I reached flat!
Don't celebrate just yet.
We still gotta get you through Elo Hell so you can join me.
I'm sorry.
I can't tell so you can join me at my rank.
I'm beginning to think there's something wrong with my head.
How do I have a migraine already?
Not funny.
I'm genuinely concerned and you laugh at me?
I've heard people our age are having all sorts of brain dysfunctions these days
and most of them are diagnosed too late to be treated.
For real?
The two of you were… a thing?
How oblivious can you be?
Well, basically.
I'm surprised you didn't catch on.
It was kind of obvious.
You're thinking grad school?
Don't sound so surprised.
I want to keep learning.
It'll give me better odds in the job market.
Oh, my lovely Xu.
For the next two years I won't be there to look after you.
So please, take care of yourself.
As if.
I'm the one who looks after you.
Honestly, this'll be like a break.
Oh, so you hate putting up with me, is that it?
Deep down, I knew the reason she decided to keep studying was to stay with Dongyi.
That tutor was the worst for real.
What were we paying the guy for?
We hardly ever saw him.
Hey now, it's in the past.
I'm serious.
She kept waiting for a sentence that never came.
Time passed in the blink of an eye, and then in a flash, two years of postgrad studies were finished.
Cheers!
You two, scoot together and I'll take a picture.
You heard the man.
Don't be shy getting closer.
I only have two photos from that night.
The other one's the selfie I took before dinner.
Stop it!
You're so annoying.
We still need the specifics of this task.
What were you hoping to find out?
I can tell you the rest of the story.
After the farewell dinner, we celebrated, like, pretty hard.
And I may have gotten drunk.
Or wasted.
Oh?
Do something naughty.
Why do you always have to think the worst?
Later!
See you guys next time.
Don't forget about me, gut-patcher.
I love everyone around.
I love these really friends.
Bye!
Don't be a stranger, don't you?
Okay.
Later.
No!
The night's still yawn!
Let's party!
But everybody already left, so...
Not true.
You're here.
I think it's about time I should be heading home.
You get to have fun.
Let them all leave.
But you're not allowed to go anywhere, understand?
Uh...
Listen.
There's something I've been meaning to tell you for a while.
Ugh!
And that's when my drunk brain decided to black out!
I have no idea what he said next, but it seemed like it was super important!
Ever since I woke up the next morning, I felt like such an idiot!
I regret it so much!
You could always just talk to him now.
You know?
Sober?
I'm way too embarrassed.
I don't have the guts to.
I'm afraid after that night, I've ruined things.
So dramatic.
Got it.
We should be able to help you out.
Easy.
Oh, we can?
Really?
I don't know.
I have no idea what he said next, but it seemed like it was super important!
Ever since I woke up the next morning, I felt like such an idiot!
I regret it so much!
You could always just talk to him now.
You know?
Sober?
I'm way too embarrassed.
I don't have the guts to.
I'm afraid after that night, I've ruined things.
So dramatic.
Got it.
We should be able to help you out.
Easy.
Oh, we can?
Really?
We'll do this, but not save people?
Also, she's not gonna pay!
Look at him!
They're taking advantage of our friendship!
You jerk!
I'll kill you!
I'm just trying to help my debt to you, so why not subtract from that?!
Idiot.
Should've hit him harder.
I'm confused.
I know they need photos, but how do they get information from them?
I wish I knew the answer to that.
They won't let anyone see them work.
It's a mystery.
Yeah.
Can't say I have much faith in that loudmouth.
I just hope he doesn't end up doing anything stupid.
There's no justice in this world!
How do you get away with beating someone you have to help you?!
Hold on a second!
Nah, he's a tool.
Lou's the one in charge.
I can assure you he's reliable.
You're in good hands.
What are you doing?
You are such a child.
My payment is making her look like the dumbest person in the world now that I'm in her body.
Oops!
Is this embarrassing?
That's a shame.
I've got good news.
There are these two internships at my mom's hospital.
And she said that if we were dating, then she could get you one of the spots.
The thing is, she doesn't like girls with long hair, so...
Huh?
What did you say?
You could've just said no thanks and let me down easy, dammit!
You're heartless!
Well, that was weird.
Guess the guy wasn't as tough as he looked.
Crybaby can't take a choke.
Please, stop.
We don't want to draw unnecessary attention.
Do I need to go over the rules again?
Please?
No.
I'd rather die.
Hey, uh...
Can I take a seat?
This feeling...
Her heart is beating so much faster than it was a second ago.
It's kind of uncomfortable.
Hey!
Hands on the table.
For sure.
You don't need to ask.
You say that.
But the last thing I want to face is your bad temper.
You two, scoot together and I'll take a picture.
You heard the man.
Don't be shy getting closer.
There's no way we're calling this a night until you've serenaded us. Come on!
You got it. Pick any song!
What's up with you today?
You usually don't drink this much, do you?
Her nerves are so bad that I can't not drink.
And you'll drink more later.
It's not going to be pretty.
I'm starting to understand how she got so smashed.
Why don't you give me this one?
Your worries aren't so bad that you need to drown your sorrows, are they?
Ugh, nerd.
Why are you always so rational?
Try following your heart and being spontaneous.
Question.
Do you know why I decided to study more?
Uh...
Not a clue.
Because I got used to being with you.
Eating our meals together.
Walking to classes.
Playing games.
The countless hours we walked aimlessly around the campus.
Talking about nothing and everything with perfect understanding.
You see...
Post-grad studies were a way for me to keep that going.
But...
Now it's coming to an end.
An end?
I'm way too embarrassed.
I don't have the guts to.
I'm afraid I might have accidentally ruined things between us.
Here's a mic!
Good night.
I...
You...
How are you doing it by yourself?
It will never work that way.
Try using your brain before attacking.
You have to wait for us to be ready.
Yeah, but if you just followed my lead,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Can you at least try to seem excited?
It looks like you're about to go to a funeral.
Hey, let me see.
If my handsome mug is blurry,
we're taking another one.
Please go away.
Come back.
I never want to see this place again.
From now on, it's up to you
to take care of our girl, Dongmi.
Wow, kind of bonkers
we're both doing post-grad work.
Isn't it?
You think so?
That's not too weird.
Plenty of our classmates will be joining us.
You are no fun.
I don't think so.
That's not too weird.
Plenty of our classmates will be joining us.
You are no fun.
Tomorrow morning's class is in Building 201.
I'll save the seats if you bring the food.
No problem.
Two fried eggs, sausage,
and a dash of hot sauce.
My greatest hope
is that I never have to say goodbye to her.
Oh damn, I didn't realize you could sing so well.
Why'd you hide that voice?
Not too shabby. I'm impressed.
Her heart goes into overdrive when he talks.
Only one thing to do!
Hey, you're dead!
Shut the place down!
Who's going next?
Later!
Don't forget about me.
We all get rich in the future.
What a great night.
My face is really red.
Hey, are you okay?
Later.
Let's keep partying!
We've already left, so...
Not true. You're here.
I think it's about time I should be heading home.
You get to have fun.
Let everybody leave.
But you're not allowed to go anywhere, Kay.
If you can stay alert, I should be able to receive the message.
Listen, there's something I've been meaning to tell you.
Graduation was close.
My folks called.
They insisted I move back home.
That guy in the hat.
Why does he look familiar?
The serial killer from the photo?
I've known for a while that I can't stay in the city after I'm done with school.
What are you doing?
Hey!
I can't let him escape!
Did you need something?
Dammit! My head is spinning!
Where are you going?
Go back. Have you lost your mind?
I think I saw the suspect from the police photo.
Don't be stupid.
You can't catch him on your own.
That guy is far more trouble than a human trafficker.
Yeah?
But if I can get a clear photo of his face, maybe we can ID him and keep him from killing again.
Crap.
Where's my phone?
Watch out!
Wait!
If you turn around too fast, he might get spooked and hurt you.
Hold on for now.
Easy for you to say.
Make him think twice.
Do something crazy.
Then make a move.
Right.
Here goes.
Oh no.
I gotta pee bad.
I'm about to burst shouldn't have had those last few rounds.
Dammit.
I forgot I'm a girl right now.
Find another way.
He's going to attack me while I'm puking?
This guy's a monster.
I have to fight him.
Oh god.
It's real.
You're in the clear.
Is he still there?
Nope.
Take this!
I was just trying to help.
Not that it looks like you needed it.
Oh, wait.
It's you.
Sorry.
There was a…
Huh?
Is that the mama's boy from earlier?
They're saying it's a case of unrequited love that went horribly wrong.
How the hell did this end up spiraling so far out of control?
So lame.
Now she's going to get hounded with a million questions
because these idiot reporters wanted a big scandal.
They even published her picture!
Did you figure out what he said?
No, got distracted.
I wrote out a report for you.
I always knew you were reliable.
Damn!
I forgot you would've caught that.
What did Dongyi say to her back then?
I already took the liberty of passing this info on to the client.
He said this.
I have something to tell you.
When graduation was close, my folks called.
They insisted I move back home.
I've known for a while that I can't stay in the city after I'm done with school.
Hi there!
I never dared to confess my feelings because I was afraid of hurting the girl I've had by my side for so long.
Just worried about my exams.
That's not healthy.
I'm having a movie night with Chao Ling to take my mind off him.
Wanna come?
Sorry.
I need to study.
Then, hold on to these for me.
I'll swing by your dorm and get them tonight.
Hey!
Make sure you're not too late or I'll have to throw them down from my window.
You two are like an old married couple.
Why not just tell them you wanna be official?
Now that school's over, I've finally realized that I want to be with you, no matter what.
Because leaving you would be a pain I could not bear.
This morning, he had an important interview at the union building.
He asked her to go with him.
He wants to make sure she feels the same.
I gotta know how everything went.
So, what's the deal?
How'd it go?
Wow!
That was fast!
Oh yay!
Things went smoothly!
Hey!
Dongyi!
You're interviewing too?
It's almost ten.
Better head up or you'll be late.
Yeah.
I'm right behind you.
See you there!
Did my confession upset her somehow?
Hm?
Did you get this confusing group message from her too?
Chialing!
You gotta call her!
Uh, right.
Hey!
What gives?
We don't understand what you're trying to tell us.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I'll be there.
As promised.
Hey, what gives? We don't understand what you're trying to tell us.
I'll be there, as promised.
Here's another six hour.
I can run out and do this well.
20 months, I think again I just don't want to die.
Well, maybe I should quit overthinking.
I'll see you as were able to look at my holdover.
Oh no, he's over again.
God without having a Sindhi Lee Wireless.
No worries, and how many fingers were hidden?
Really stop thinking about it!
Stop thinking about it!
Stop thinking about it Stop stop thinking about it While your mind overclouded
脱离现实的梦境化危机 Oh
始终的我需要怎样才能自保 So stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it Stop stop thinking about it While your mind overclouded
在这时间的风险停止思考
我明白多少烦恼都是庸人自饶
Stop thinking about it Stop thinking about it Stop stop thinking about it While your mind overclouded
Yeah